equifaxsecurity2017.com 2019-09-15

# Privacy Policy - 2017 Cybersecurity Incident & Important Consumer Information

**Effective Date: September 15, 2017**

Protecting your personal information is important to Equifax. Please review the following information regarding our privacy policies and practices.

This online privacy policy (“Policy”) applies to this Equifax Inc. website and related websites that link or refer to this policy (collectively and individually, “Website”), and we want visitors to our Website to understand our privacy practices in connection with this Website.

Please note that if you decide to check the potential impact of the 2017 Cybersecurity Incident (the “Incident”) on your personal information or enroll in the free identity theft monitoring that we are offering as a result of the Incident, that monitoring is offered subject to the privacy policy that appears on the separate website where you perform those activities.

**This document includes information about:**

  1. Information We Collect and How We Use It
  2. How We Share Information
  3. Information Security
  4. Your Choice and Control Over Your Information
  5. Third Party Websites and Services
  6. Users Outside the United States
  7. Changes to this Policy
  8. How to Contact Us

**Special Note for Parents:**  This Website is a general audience website and is not designed or intended to attract children younger than 13. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is younger than 13.

**1\. Information We Collect and How We Use It**

The information we gather from you enables us to operate and make improvements to our Website. The information we collect from you includes information collected automatically, such as through cookies or other technology.

_**We will never sell the information collected from this site.**_

However, we will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, and enhance your user experience.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We may receive and store certain types of information automatically when you interact with our Website.

**Cookies:**  We use session and persistent cookie technology. Generally speaking, cookies are text files that are placed in your device’s browser. Cookies can be used to help recognize your browser across different web pages, websites, and browsing sessions and to personalize and improve your experience on the Website.

Our Website may use Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, in order to better understand your use of our Website and how we can make improvements. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit a website, what pages you visit when you do so, and what other websites you used prior to coming to such website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit a website, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with your personal information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit a website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Website is governed by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

**Web Beacons:**  We use a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our website by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

**Log Files:**  Equifax may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, computer MAC address, Equifax cookie information, device and browser information, the page you requested and the time of your page request. Our servers may automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our website and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. Equifax uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the website so that we can make the website appealing to as many customers as possible, and improve those features.

**Device identification:**  We also may collect other information about the device you use to access our Website. The information may include device type, unique device identification (if applicable), operating system, browser used, device model number, serial number, and types and versions of software installed. We may also collect your IP address, which is a number automatically assigned to your device when you access the Internet and can be used to derive your general geolocation. This information is used to create a digital identifier for your device that may be associated with your account.

**Information we collect from others:**

We may receive information from third parties that identifies your interactions with our Website across multiple devices.

We may combine all of the information we collect or receive from you and use or disclose it in the manner described in this online privacy policy, including to help us better tailor content and offers to your interests and needs.

**2\. How We May Share Information**

We understand that the privacy of your personal information is important. As a result, we will keep the information obtained through this Website within Equifax except where disclosure is required by law or as described in this privacy policy.

**Affiliates:**  We work closely with our affiliate, TrustedID, to offer you free credit file monitoring and identity theft protection in connection with the Incident and may share the information collected about you on the Website in connection with that offering.

**Service Providers:**  We may employ affiliates, other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf such as hosting or providing content updates to this Website. Unless we tell you differently, our service providers do not have any right to use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

**Business Transfers:**  If all or part of our company is sold or merged, if we make a sale or transfer of assets, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, we may transfer your information, including your personal information, to one or more third parties as part of that transaction.

**Protection of You, Equifax and Others:**  We reserve the right to disclose your information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Equifax, our employees, our customers, or others.

**3\. Information Security**

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information and use technical, administrative and physical security measures that comply with applicable federal and state laws. However, no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect the personal information we maintain, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that is collected on this Website.

**4\. Your Choice and Control Over Your Information**

**Do Not Track signal:**  Some web browsers may transmit “do not track” signals to the websites and other online services with which a user communicates. There is no industry standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. We currently do not take action in response to these signals. If and when a standard is established and accepted, we may revisit our policy on responding to these signals.

**Your California Privacy Rights:**  California Civil Code Section 1798.83 entitles California customers to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies may contact us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section.

**5\. Third Party Web Sites and Services**

This Privacy Policy applies only to this Website. This site may contain links or referrals to other websites not operated or controlled by Equifax (“Third Party Websites”). The policies and procedures that are described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to Third Party Websites, and any links or referrals from Equifax do not imply that Equifax endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Websites. We suggest contacting those third parties directly for information on their privacy policies and practices.

**6\. Users Outside the United States**

This Website is intended for users within the United States. If you use this Website from outside the United States, please be aware that information you provide to Equifax or that Equifax obtains as a result of your use of this Website may be processed and transferred to the United States and be subject to the laws of the United States. The privacy and data protection laws in the United States may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using our Website, using any of our Website’s functions or features, or by providing us with your personal information or non-personal information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of your information in and to the United States.

**7\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may change this Policy in the future. If we make changes to this Policy, we will post the revised privacy policy and its effective date on this Website.

**8\. How to Contact Us**

If you have questions or comments about this Policy, please e-mail us at [privacy@Equifax.com](mailto:privacy@Equifax.com) or write to Chief Privacy Officer, Equifax Inc., 1550 Peachtree Street, NW, Atlanta, GA 30309. Please reference “Privacy Notice – EquifaxSecurity2017,” when contacting us about this policy.
